TAP version 13
# Subtest: long guides have one title, unique anchors, and a working HTML outline
ok 1 - long guides have one title, unique anchors, and a working HTML outline
  ---
  duration_ms: 13.0326
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: markup preserves code and supports accessible tables without JavaScript
ok 2 - markup preserves code and supports accessible tables without JavaScript
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.7686
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: raw HTML and unsafe link destinations cannot execute
ok 3 - raw HTML and unsafe link destinations cannot execute
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6212
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: legacy plain headings remain readable and incomplete fences stay escaped
ok 4 - legacy plain headings remain readable and incomplete fences stay escaped
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0821
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: article examples allow local raster images and escape captions and unsafe sources
ok 5 - article examples allow local raster images and escape captions and unsafe sources
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.0444
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: quick creation cannot publish an empty article and still creates drafts
ok 6 - quick creation cannot publish an empty article and still creates drafts
  ---
  duration_ms: 376.7667
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: analytics throttles before writes, isolates its quota, and rejects unknown tools
ok 7 - analytics throttles before writes, isolates its quota, and rejects unknown tools
  ---
  duration_ms: 48.9216
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: analytics ignores spoofed forwarded-for and fails closed without the Vercel address
ok 8 - analytics ignores spoofed forwarded-for and fails closed without the Vercel address
  ---
  duration_ms: 18.8321
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: admins create confirmed password accounts without invitation links
ok 9 - admins create confirmed password accounts without invitation links
  ---
  duration_ms: 28.0472
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: article saves return useful validation errors for missing references
ok 10 - article saves return useful validation errors for missing references
  ---
  duration_ms: 55.3324
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..10
# tests 10
# suites 0
# pass 10
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 2429.6256
